Contact

West Jordan, UT, 84088

(786) 332-7155

florhaideeg@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/florhaidee/

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/florhaidee/

Skills

UI Improvements



Organizational Skills



Analytical Skills



Troubleshooting



Front End Web Development



Code Debugging



Software

HTML



CSS



Bootstrap



Materialize



JQuery





Florhaidee **Guerra**

Full Stack Web Developer

Bilingual, Front end Developer with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction.

Experience building products with responsive design, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, control of versions, usability and speed. Ability to respond to challenges by translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs and third-party integrations.

Work History

2015-08 -2016-07

2012-05 -

2012-08

Junior Software Test Engineer

Xpectra Remote Management, Bolivar, Venezuela

- Collaborated with inter-departmental teams and subcontractors to verify accurate application of prescribed testing protocols.
- Strong skills in defined and tracked quality assurance metrics, including test results, defect counts and performance discrepancies and delivering on time.
- Wrote and optimized test cases to maximize success of manual software testing with consistent, thorough approaches and managed to deliver results 100% on time.
- Operated under Agile and Scrum frameworks to complete releases every week and well-organized sprints.
- Worked with different projects at same time.
 Managing all with same focused and responsibility.

Java Developer - Professional Internship

Orinoco Steelmaker SIDOR, Puerto Ordaz, Venezuela

First person to investigated new and emerging

JavaScript



Languages

Spanish



- software applications within Business Rules practice to design, select, implement and use new software application for business rules including Drools and use Agile methodological.
- Managed all information gathered and developed new prototype of shopping pricing model based on management of business rules in less than 1 month.
- Tested troubleshooting methods, devised innovative solutions, and documented resolutions for inclusion in knowledge base for support team use.

Education

2020-04 -	Coding Bootcamp: Full Stack Web
Current	Developer
	University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UTContinuing education in Web development
2006-03 - 2012-07	Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering
	National Experimental University of Guayana -
	Venezuela